worldoffemale.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy

World of female, INC tries to employ the various positive aspects of modern web technology, to protect the information provided by you. The purpose of this privacy policy is to create awareness about the information capture by the site. The information provided by you is used for the specified objective and we will not distribute this critical information with any third party user. Various security mechanisms are implemented by the company to safeguard this vital information. This privacy policy states the intent of gathering the information and the various methods of information capture implemented by the site. The provided information will be used in accordance with the terms and conditions stated in the privacy policy. By using this site, you imply that you are in accordance with the privacy policy.

**What information do we actually gather?**

Detailed data; which is unique for every user is collected by the site. This information provided by a user may be kept in our records for further use. This may comprise of the vital information required for the specified purpose. Fields which may be retained from the user information are records such as name, age, gender, email address, residential information and many others.

The state information of a user is required for multiple purposes. Hence we use the web technology system of transmitting cookies. Cookies are required for the purpose of authenticating the identity of the user and to keep a track of the user’s browsing routine. A cookie is sent to the user’s browser which is then returned in an unaffected state by the browser. Cookies do not store any user related information and are simply present for enhancing the experience of the user.

When you post your views on a topic, other registered members of the website have the right to comment on your views.  You can use your social networking profile to comment on the posts as well.  The social networking profile is not made available for public discretion.

Apart from the above mentioned information, we may even assemble some other information for technical purpose. This information assists us in determining the popularity of our website. This aggregated data is not user-specific and is collected with the sole intention of enhancing the capability of our website. This information is captured in the form of a Log file. A log file keeps the track of all the data which is being transmitted from your browser.

**How is the collected information used?**

The collected information is used only for the specified purpose. If you use the “contact us” option, then you will be required to enter your contact details. We will then establish contact with you, by making use of these details. If you choose to register with us, then the details provided by you are critical to authenticate your account.  We may distribute the personal information provided by you with our third party affiliates, with the sole intention of your benefit in mind. Prior mention of the distribution of the information, with a third party will be provided. If you wish to provide your information, you can accept the condition on that service.

**What if I provide my information to a marketing affiliate of the site?**

When you click on the link of a marketing affiliate’s website; you will get redirected to our partner’s website. The privacy policy provided here is valid only for this website. Hence we are not responsible for safeguarding the information provided to the other websites. Your information will be under the supervision of the affiliate’s website, with whom you are interacting. Read the privacy policy posted on the website before providing the personal information. This policy is solely maintained for the worldoffemale.com website and does not have any relation with any third party links posted on the website.

**The critical information provided by me is kept securely?**

We try to implement the best security mechanisms in order to keep the data provided by our users securely. Encryption mechanisms and several security barriers are used to keep the information secure. There are always some doubts about the security mechanisms though. The information may be prone to attacks. If there are some doubts in your mind about the integrity of the data provided by you, then providing a feedback to us is the best option. We will ensure that the best security methods are kept in place to prevent the vulnerability of the vital information. We would like to stress that such a situation has rarely happened before and the information provided to us, is always safeguarded with great interest.

**What if I get subscription letters/emails from the site to provide my contact information?**

Newsletters are sent from the official site, just to inform the members about the latest developments. If any such email tries to extract vital personal information, then it must be treated as a bogus attempt. Report any such fraudulent attempt by providing a feedback to us. Do not provide any information to such subscriptions from the affiliated/non-affiliated links.

**What if I do not provide certain information which I deem to be confidential?**

When you use this site, it implies that you agree with the privacy policy. You can however decline to provide certain information, which you consider too private to disclose. If you refuse to fill in some mandatory details then you may be unable to take the benefit of some functions present on the site.

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising.**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Privacy system for children**

We understand that young children are susceptible to providing personal details easily. The site employs an age limit of 13 years and above. People, who fall in the specified age group are allowed to provide their information.

**About Images In Our Website** : Most of the images used in our website and from various sources. Since we have different authors they may use images from sites like flick, google images, free stock photos etc. We always try our best to give Image Credit to each image. If you own any of the images used in our website and don’t allow us to use then kindly contact us at : admin[at]worldoffemale.com  If you copy images from our website, kindly give credit to original image source that we have used.

**About DoubleClick/Google Adsense Ads** : Google as a third party vender  uses a special [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx "DART Cookie Description")  to serve ads on our website and other websites. If you don’t want to have this DART cookie on your computer, [you can opt out](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Ad Privacy") .

**Right to change the privacy policy**

The right to change the privacy policy is exclusively reserved by the website. If we make some alterations in the original privacy policy, we will keep you updated.  If you persist with the site after the revised policy has been implemented, it implies that you agree with the new privacy policy.

Please Read our [Terms Of Use](https://www.worldoffemale.com/terms/)

Thank you for reading the privacy policy and we sincerely hope you will abide by it.
